{
  "extraDescription": "Recall squares of 0-20",
  "randomQuestionCount": 3,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "7&sup2;",
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "question": "3&sup2;",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "5&sup2;",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "question": "16&sup2;",
      "answer": "256"
    },
    {
      "question": "8&sup2;",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "17&sup2;",
      "answer": "289"
    },
    {
      "question": "4&sup2;",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "14&sup2;",
      "answer": "196"
    },
    {
      "question": "15&sup2;",
      "answer": "225"
    },
    {
      "question": "11&sup2;",
      "answer": "121"
    },
    {
      "question": "19&sup2;",
      "answer": "361"
    },
    {
      "question": "12&sup2;",
      "answer": "144"
    },
    {
      "question": "13&sup2;",
      "answer": "169"
    },
    {
      "question": "6&sup2;",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "18&sup2;",
      "answer": "324"
    },
    {
      "question": "10&sup2;",
      "answer": "100"
    },
    {
      "question": "0&sup2;",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "20&sup2;",
      "answer": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "1&sup2;",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "9&sup2;",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "question": "2&sup2;",
      "answer": "4"
    }
  ]
}
